Don't do this to me.
لا تفعل هذا بي.
Your Excellency, why did you wronged
معالي الوزير لماذا ظلمت
your Excellency?
امتيازك؟
Young master is awake.
السيد الشاب مستيقظ.
Darn it.
رتقها.
It's so hateful.
إنه مكروه للغاية.
I can't believe I fell for such a low-end trick.
لا أصدق أنني وقعت في مثل هذه الحيلة المنخفضة.
Darn it.
رتقها.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
It's okay.
لا بأس.
How could I be okay?
كيف يمكنني أن أكون بخير؟
Nothing happened.
لم يحدث شيء.
You really scared me.
لقد أخفتني حقًا.
It's all my fault.
هذا كله خطأي.
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
Merman blood
دم حوريات البحر
can resist all kinds of poisons.
يمكنه مقاومة جميع أنواع السموم.
It's true.
انها حقيقة.
I'll poison you to death at any time.
سأسممك حتى الموت في أي وقت.
Fu Su
فو سو
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
these are all the letters I got from Chen Moxi.
هذه هي كل الرسائل التي تلقيتها من تشين موكسي.
Now that she has been assassinated,
الآن وقد اغتيلت ،
she may die soon.
قد تموت قريبا.
It must be just an abandoned child of Beiqi.
يجب أن يكون مجرد طفل مهجور لـ Beiqi.
And the one who really harmed our Daqin
والشخص الذي أضر حقا بداقين
is someone else?
هو شخص اخر
When my master was killed two months ago,
عندما قتل سيدي قبل شهرين
the murderer left the murder weapon at the scene.
ترك القاتل سلاح الجريمة في مكان الحادث.
I'm sure that
أنا متاكد أنه
the murderer must be a spy of Beiqi.
لابد أن القاتل جاسوس لبيكي.
I hope His Majesty can order a thorough investigation.
آمل أن يأمر جلالة الملك بإجراء تحقيق شامل.
I've been investigating it thoroughly
لقد كنت أحقق في الأمر بدقة
State Preceptor
مدرس الدولة
What else do you want me to give you?
ماذا تريد مني أن أعطيك أيضًا؟
I guess,
اعتقد،
the mastermind behind this scene must be an important official in the court.
العقل المدبر وراء هذا المشهد يجب أن يكون مسؤولا مهما في المحكمة.
I hope,
آمل،
we can search the residences of all the officials above Grade 1,
يمكننا تفتيش مساكن جميع المسؤولين فوق الدرجة الأولى ،
Ridiculous.
سخيف.
Grand Tutor asks to see you,
يطلب Grand Tutor رؤيتك ،
Announce it.
أعلن عنها.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
تحياتي جلالة الملك.
Grand Tutor,
المعلم الكبير ،
can you read this letter?
هل تستطيع قراءة هذه الرسالة
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
this letter is heavily encrypted,
هذه الرسالة مشفرة بشكل كبير ،
I really don't understand.
أنا حقا لا أفهم.
And this dagger
وهذا الخنجر
is made by the caudal fin of Yan Chu, the most beautiful woman in the South China Sea.
مصنوعة من الزعنفة الذيلية ليان تشو ، أجمل امرأة في بحر الصين الجنوبي.
Are you serious?
هل أنت جاد؟
I like to collect world-famous paintings,
أحب أن أجمع اللوحات ذات الشهرة العالمية ،
among which,
من بينها،
There is a portrait of Yan Chu,
هناك صورة ليان تشو ،
and,
و،
She is the biological mother of Fusu, a merman.
هي الأم البيولوجية لفوسو ، حوري البحر.
The merman must have some ulterior motive
يجب أن يكون للحوري بعض الدوافع الخفية
to approach the State Preceptor.
للاقتراب من مدرس الدولة.
Your Majesty, please put him in prison
جلالة الملك ، يرجى وضعه في السجن
and interrogate Yan Chu's whereabouts,
واستجواب مكان يان تشو ،
Revenge for my master.
الانتقام لسيدي.
That makes sense.
منطقي.
Put the merman into the prison,
ضع الحوري في السجن ،
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،